(Howard:)If y'all don't mind,
I got a hankering for a Lone Star Beer.
(Mrs Cooper:)There's no alcohol in this household,
stop talking like that and lose the hat.
(Howard:)Sorry. I'll take a diet Yoo-hoo
if you have it.
(Mrs Cooper:)You'll take a cola.
What about you? Raj, is it?
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, you still having trouble talking
to the ladies? Ha-ha-ha.
(Mrs Cooper:)Because, you know, at our church...
(Mrs Cooper:)...we have a woman
who's an amazing healer.
Mostly she does crutch
and wheelchair people...
(Mrs Cooper:)...but I bet she'd be willing
to take a shot...
...at whatever Third-World demon
is running around inside of you.
If you don't mind, there's a 3:05
nonstop back to Los Angeles...
...and you have no idea
how much I wanna be on it.
(Mrs Cooper:)-A girl?
-Uh, yes, ma'am.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, good. I've been praying for you.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)What are they doing here?